女士们先生们 欢迎来到伊拉克利翁【希腊克里特岛的城市】
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Heraklion.
当地时间凌晨3点 气温28摄氏度
The local time is 3 am,
and the temperature is 28 degrees Celsius.
直到飞机完全停稳前
Please remain in your seats
请各位乘客不要离开自己的位置
until the aircraft has
come to a complete standstill
机长已经关闭"系好安全带"的指示灯
and the captain has switched
off the "fasten seat belt" sign.
请各位乘客小心头顶的行李
Please take care when opening the overhead bins
因为物品可能在飞行过程中滑落
as items may have
been dislodged during the flight.
感谢您搭乘我们的航班
We thank you for flying with us today
期待再次跟您相见
and look forward to seeing you again soon.
如有转机或未到最终目的地
Please check with ground staff for connecting flights
请和地勤人员沟通
or further travel to your final destination.
马利亚 我们来了【希腊克里特岛小镇】
Say uh, ah, Malia!
我来告诉你为什么我这么累
I'll tell you why I'm so tired.
- 都是因为你 艾姆  - 为什么
- That would be you, Em.
- Why?
你现在还问"为什么" 那在她订票的时候呢
What do you mean, "why"?
What about when she was booking the holiday?
你什么都没做 就会说"我累了"
You did no work.
All this "I'm exhausted."
我一睡醒 20多条消息 都是你发的
I woke up to 20 messages from you.
"我们必须提前四个小时到 "
"We have to be there four hours before!"
要不是我 你能到这儿吗
If it wasn't for
me, would you be here?
说啊
Would you be here?
啊 我们到啦 宝贝
Ah! We're in Malia, babe! Baby!
有点冷
It's kinda cold.
我要进去了 快点
I'm going in! Come on!
哦 她要进来了 她要进来了
Oh, she's in! She's in! She's in!
我觉得我们不应该这样
I don't think we should do this.
我没想到天气会这么冷
I don't think it's
supposed to be this cold.
你会习惯的
You'll get used to it.
♪ 天哪 天哪 当我看到你我就该跑
♪ Oh my God, oh my God
When I see you I should run
♪ 我说着自己从未说过的话 做着自己从未做过的事
♪ I'm saying things I've never
said Doing things I've never done
我他妈的爱死你们了
I fucking love you guys.
- 我他妈爱死你们了  - 真这是有史以来最好的假期
- I fucking love you guys!
- Best holiday ever!
哦 不 我的烟
Oh, no, look at my fags!
哪儿呢
Where?
快点儿 一会儿都湿了
I'll get them,
I'll get them!
不 天啊 我的天啊
No! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
抱歉
I'm so sorry.
太冷了
It's so cold.
妈的
What the fuck?
旅程顺利吗
X
啊 他妈的
Ah, fuck's sake!
给我放一根烟 我的都抽不了了
Set me a fag.
Mine are fucked.
要是飞机上能打电话的话 我妈肯定会打的
I swear my mum would've called
on the plane if she could have.
我都不确定她知不知道我们已经离开了
I'm not sure Mum's even clocked we've left.
就剩这几根了吗
This is all we
have between all of us?
- 是的 就剩一根了  - 怎么 你是要把它晒干吗
- Yeah, just one.
- This is it to get dry?
- 我他妈快饿死了  - 你天天都这么说
- Guys, I'm fucking starving.
- I swear you're always hungry.
为什么海水会这么冷
Why is the sea so cold?
我们还有很多时间可以消磨
You know we still got
loads of time to kill?
你想要薯条吗
Do you wanna get chips?
- 当然 当然  - 薯条 薯条 薯条
- Yes, 100%.
- Chips! Chips! Chips!
- 我要大份的  - 大份 超大的
- I want a big fucking big portion.
- Large! Large, large, extra-large.
哦 对不起
Oh, excuse me.
抱歉 嗯...
Sorry, um...
我就是想问一下我们能不能要个特殊点儿的房间 嗯...
I was just wondering if maybe we
could have a room with, like, a...
比如说 能看见泳池之类的
like, a pool view?
泳池吗 抱歉
Pool view? No, no, no.
已经被订完了
All gone. I'm sorry.
好吧 嗯...
OK. Um...
我尽力了 但是都已经订完了
I tried. Apparently, they're all gone.
你好
Hi!
- 你好 - 嗯 我叫塔拉
- Hi.
- Um, my name's Tara.
- 很高兴见到你  - 很高兴见到你
- Nice to meet you.
嗯 所以 问题是… 抱歉 我口水都出来了
Um, so, the thing is...
I just spat, sorry.
可是我们真的很需要那样的房间
Um, the thing is, we're
going to need pool view,
因为...你看到我们的朋友斯凯了吗 就在那儿
because... see our friend Skye there?
她不太会游泳
She can't swim very well,
所以我们得时刻看着她
so we need to, like, keep
eyes on her at all times.
- 一刻都不能放松  - 这样万一她出事儿了 我们才能马上救她
- Like, we have to see her.
- We can be lifeguards.
这样就能避免那些糟糕的情况发生
We can just dive in if anything happens.
我们都是游泳健将 真的
We're excellent swimmers, like, really good.
- 这样能省去你们很多的麻烦  - 其实我还代表市里参过赛呢
- Save you guys the trouble.
- I actually swim for the county.
我们希望能好好利用这个假期
We were hoping we could use this holiday
去教教她...
to help teach her...
起码也得学会狗刨吧
to doggy-paddle.
- 好吧 好吧  - 谢谢
- All right, all right.
- Thanks.
我的天啊 这也太好了吧
Oh, my God!
This is insane!
天啊
Oh, my God!
看看这只天鹅
Look at this swan!
- 我太喜欢这些窗帘了  - 居然还有天鹅
- I fucking love the curtains.
- He left us swans.
- 塔兹...  - 哦 宝贝 太棒了
- Taz...
- Oh, babe, stunning!
没有比这更美的了...
Outfit number one sorted!
Outfit number...
哦 还有蝴蝶
Oh, there's butterflies everywhere as well!
嘿…斯凯 你在干什么
Um... Skye!
What are you doing?
你在干什么
- 炒烟啊 - 你真疯
- Deep-fried fags.
- You're a nutter!
- 但是给我也来一份 谢谢 - 它们已经干了
- But I will have one, thank you. OK.
- They are already dry.
- 我们还有自己的冰箱  - 真他妈的奢侈
- We got our own fridge!
- Fucking luxury.
这个房间也太大了 简直了
This room is huge!
Like, a whole room.
在哪里 让我来看看
Where? Let's see.
啊 泳池
Ey! Pool view!
我看看
Let me see!
这是我这辈子见过最美的景色了 呼
Best view I've ever
seen in my life! Whoo!
抱歉 但我需要我的甜甜圈
Sorry about that, but I needed my doughnut.
早餐
Breakfast!
还是…早餐
And... breakfast!
晚餐也来一个
Dinner one!
- 妈的 不好意思了  - 你能不这样吗
- Shit! Sorry.
- Can you not?
上床最多的人就能赢得这个
Oi, whoever gets laid the most wins this.
做爱的时候还能用到苹果潘趣酒吗
Apple punch for sex?
- 不不不不  - 实际上...
- No. No, no, no.
- Actually...
快看这个
This.
奶头儿杯子
Titty glasses.
那最烂的的那个人会得到什么
What do we get
if we're sick the most?
什么都没有
Um, nothing,
我们才不会为那个做什么计划的 你个蠢蛋
because we're not going to
plan for that, you nutter.
好吧 好吧
All right. All right.
额外奖励
Bonus prize.
我们是派对女郎
Party girl!
嘿 我一直在想
Guys, I've been thinking,
谁上床最多 就应该睡主卧
whoever's getting laid the most, they
should kinda get the main room.
其他人的话
And everyone else
摸到哪里就在哪儿睡吧
just kinda sleep where they land.
反正我这个假期就是能不睡就不睡
Me, I'm going to be
refraining from sleep this holiday.
得了吧 你肯定会在俱乐部里睡着的
Don't lie! You're going to
be, like, asleep in the club.
哇 你看起来真漂亮
Oi, you look beaut!
来吧 试试这个
Come here, try this.
你应该就这样出去
You should just go out like that.
就这样吗
Like this?
无论你穿什么 看起来都很潮
You look banging no matter what you wear.
能借我点唇彩吗
Can I borrow some of that lip gloss?
我来给你涂
Yeah, let me do it for you.
哇
Look at you.
如果这个假期你都没跟别人上过床 那你这辈子都没戏了
If you don't get laid on
this holiday then you never will.
不行 我可不能到死都是处女
No, I can't die a virgin!
他妈的
Fuck!
等等 我们还没准备好
Wait, wait, wait, we're not ready.
你们都是哪儿来的
Whereabouts you all from?
我们可没有零钱
We don't have any change.
怎么 我看起来像是无家可归还是什么吗
What, am I homeless or something?
♪ 打电话给我
♪ Call me
♪ 呼喊我的名字
♪ Call me by my name
♪ 或者用我的号码给我打电话
♪ Or call me by my number
♪ 是你让我经历了这一切
♪ You put me through it
♪ 我还是会按照自己的方式做事
♪ I'll still be doing
it the way I do it
♪ 然而 你却试图让我忘记
♪ And yet, you
try to make me forget
♪ 我到底是谁
♪ Who I really am
♪ 我是独一无二的
♪ I am the one and only
♪ ...永远都是
♪ ...all this time
♪ 我尝试过有尊严地离开... ♪
♪ I've tried to walk with dignity... ♪
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
不是这样的 放着吧
Not like that!
Give it here!
- 我太渴了  - 塔拉
- I'm too thirsty. Hmm.
- Tara.
我有点儿想吐
I'm going to be sick.
出来的第一晚 艾姆就吐了
Night one in the Big Brother house,
Em is sick.
妈的 她真的吐了
Fuck! She's actually going to be sick.
拿住麦克风
Hold the microphone.
♪ 我是独一无二的 ♪
♪ I am the one and only ♪
我们能再来三杯吗
Can we have three more shots, please?
我爱你 塔兹
I love you, Taz.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
一辈子的朋友 对吧
Besties for life, yeah?
我刚刚去了吧台又拿了几杯
I've just been to
the bar and got shots.
来吧
Check it out.
不不不
No, no, no.
来吧
Yes!
哎呀 如果我每次考试都不及格怎么办
Oi, what happens if I fail every exam?
去他妈的学校 大家一起找工作吧
Fuck school!
Let's all just find jobs together.
你真他妈聪明
You're fucking smart.
我肯定都会失败
I'm actually going to fail.
塔兹 哪怕你一败涂地
Taz, even if you failed everything,
你也可以靠着自己的口才闯出一条路的
you could talk your way in.
- 塔拉  - 我要尿尿
- Tara!
- I need a wee.
严格来说 薯片也是蔬菜吧 不是吗
Chips are technically vegetables, aren't they?
斯凯 该轮到我吐了吗
Skye, is it my
night to throw up yet?
你已经吐了
You already threw up.
别笑我
Don't laugh at me!
塔拉
Tara!
如果我上了一所好学校
What happens if I
go to this good school
但是却没人喜欢我怎么办
and then no one even
likes me when I get there?
哦 艾姆 那太傻了 别这么想
Oh, Em, that's silly.
Don't think like that.
反正也没人喜欢你
No one likes you anyway.
不然你觉得我们为什么会和你在一起
Why do you think
we ended up with you?
- 我开玩笑呢  - 起来吧 宝贝
- I'm joking.
- Here come on babe! Babe, babe! Babe!
反正怎么都是双赢
It's, like, a win-win situation.
不然就是你失败了 留在我们这些废物身边
Either you fail and
you stay with us wasters,
- 或者...   - 我不想失败
- or...
- I don't wanna fail!
或者你成功了 然后就会变得很有钱
Or you get in
and then you're really rich
这样你每年都可以带我们去度假
and you can bring
us on holiday every year.
哪有有钱的兽医啊
Vets aren't rich.
他们都没有很多钱
They don't have loads and loads of money.
是的 但是你真的很聪明啊 你一直都是
Yeah, but you're just, like, really smart.
You always have been.
我连后空翻都不会
I can't even do a backflip.
问题是 我不知道自己想做什么
Thing is, I don't
know what I wanna do.
- 我想...  - 我想做一个后空翻
- I think...
- I wanna do a backflip.
我想我还是做生意吧 因为现在什么都是生意
I think maybe I'll just do
business, 'cause everything is business now.
每天都是这样 没什么区别
Every day, like, just all the time.
那我们得一起做生意
We got to go into business together.
我也听过这种说法
I heard that as well.
我的天啊 这些芝士薯条
Oh, my God!
These cheesy chips, man!
- 什么  - 啊
- What?
- Ow!
不然我还是开个自己的餐厅吧
Oi, I am actually going
to open my own restaurant
就只卖芝士薯条
and just serve cheesy chips.
等她大学毕业了 你就可以来给我打工了
Oi, you can come and work for
me while Em fucks off to finish school.
我会去的 每天都去
I'll come. I'll go every single day.
- 我想...  - 我会去三次
- I think...
- I'll come three times.
- 我想我们应该...  - 早饭还有晚饭的时候
- I think we should...
- Breakfast and dinner.
我觉得我们该去睡觉了
I think we should go to bed now.
我现在最该做的就是上个好的学校
All I need to do
to go to good school
拿到很好的成绩...
is if I get lots of As.
Say As in...
艾姆
Em!
- 闭嘴吧 别卷了  - 问题是 虽然...
- Shut up! You're stressing me out.
- Oi! The thing is, though...
- ...就是那个...   - 我会握紧你们的手
- ...is that...
- I'll hold it in that hand.
你们两个是我最好的朋友
...is that you two
are actually my best mates.
嗨 我是佩奇 很高兴认识你们 女士们
All right? I'm Paige.
Nice to meet you, ladies.
- 我叫帕迪  - 很高兴见到你
- My name's Paddy.
- Nice to meet you.
我还以为你把我丢给这个小丑等死呢
Oi, I thought you left me
for dead with this clown. Oi!
你知道 我非常爱你
You know, I love youse a lot,
但是如果我们总是结伴出去 谁都不会有床上的
but none of us are going to get
laid if we just hang out with each other.
昨晚简直太灾难了
Last night was a disaster.
走吧那就
Come on, then.
整个酒店的人现在肯定都在洗澡
Everyone in the entire hotel must
be having a shower right now.
喂 塔兹 你应该穿这个 会很性感
Oi, Taz, you should wear this.
You'd look so sexy in it.
你不觉得吗 艾姆
Don't you think, Em?
我不知道 看起来很不舒服
I don't know, looks mad uncomfortable to me.
斯凯 这是你的吗
Skye, is this yours?
- 是啊 怎么了   - 我可以用用吗
- Yeah, why?
- Can I borrow it?
你知道该怎么用吗
Do you know what you're doing with it?
- 知道啊 就是...  - 来吧 我告诉你
- Yeah, it's just...
- Come on, I'll show you.
其实我的机器都坏了
No my, my robot is actually sick, though.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
妈的 你看起来简直了
You look insane!
What the fuck?
真的 你看起来真的太美了
Yeah, OK, I kinda get, you look incredible.
- 啊 她已经准备好了  - 呼
- Ah, she's ready to go out!
- Whoo!
美女
Sexy!
嘿 小可人儿
Oi, smoke show!
我知道你能听到我 我能看见你在笑了
I know you can hear me.
I can see you smiling.
你一会儿要出去吗
You lot going out later?
我们这儿也有个派对 你应该过来
You should come round here for pres.
好啊 我问问她们
Yeah, I can ask the girls.
不愧是你 选择性听力是吧
Fucking hell!
Talk about selective hearing.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
塔拉
Tara.
真是个好名字
That's a nice name, innit?
我是巴杰【獾】
I'm Badger.
奇怪的名字
That's a bit of a weird name, innit?
是昵称
It's my nickname.
这是谁
Who's this?
罗密欧 罗密欧 你是几号房啊
Romeo, Romeo, where is you? Yeah.
341房间
Room 341, yeah?
放轻松 小老虎
All right, easy, Tiger.
我们才刚认识
We only just met.
- 这他妈是啥  - 什么
- Oi, no, what the fuck is that?
- What?
- 谁画的  - 我自己弄的
- Who's done that?
- I did it.
太难看了 像两条大鼻涕虫一样
They're fucking ridiculous, like two
massive slugs on your face.
你觉得他们多大了
Wait, how old do
you think they are, though?
嘿 别忘了电话 钥匙还有钱
Oi, guys, remember your
phone and keys and money.
大概19 21差不多吧
I think, maybe, like, 19, 21.
那我们怎么说 说自己18吗
Yeah, so, what are we going to say?
We're, like, 18?
你们是要坠入爱河 然后又把我扔一边吗
You guys just going to fall in
love and leave me to it again?
就说18岁 刚刚大学毕业 可以吧
I think, like, 18, just finished college, yeah?
- 很显然 我开的是宝马 - 哈 你倒是想
- Yeah, obviously I drive a BMW.
- Ha! You wish!
- 好了 来吧 塔兹  - 我应该说我正在攻读学位
- All right, come on, Taz!
- I think I'm doing a degree
一切都是为了成为下一任首相
to be the next Prime Minister.
如果你现在能告诉我现任首相是谁
Bro, if you can tell me
who the current Prime Minister is,
那我才会考虑让你接替他的工作
then I'll consider you taking his job, yeah?
说说看
Go on.
好了 妈的 别说了 快走吧
All right, for fuck's sake,
just come on! Shut up!
这看起来真的没问题吗
Does this actually look all right?
- 还是很不舒服吗  - 是的
- Mad uncomfortable, innit?
- Yeah.
不过你看起来棒极了
You look fit as fuck, though!
- 你也一样   - 快点儿
- So do you, mate.
- Quick.
- 塔兹 你的手机   - 递给我
- Taz, your phone, I said!
- Yeah, give it, then.
- 我要我的包  - 还有钥匙
- I need my bag.
- Keys!
塔兹 你得把眉毛弄干净啊
Taz, you have got
to sort those eyebrows out.
帕迪 到你了
Paddy, your go.
哪有 轮到佩奇了
Nah, it's Paige's go.
我从来没有撞上停着的汽车
Never have I ever crashed
a quad into a parked car.
巴奇今天早上还喝的醉醺醺的
Badger this morning still pissed out his head.
我一般都是这样
I'm usually a sick driver.
开货车谋生
I fucking drive vans for a living.
It's me job.
你不会在上班的时候撞到那些停着的车吧
You don't crash them into parked
cars at work, though, do you?
我从来没有过三人行
Never have I ever had a threesome.
- 已经喝光了  - 再拿一些吧
- Get shots out.
- Yeah, let's get some shots.
给你来一杯
There's one.
- 干杯  - 干杯
- Cheers.
转起来 加速 快点儿
Spin, spin.
Faster, faster, faster, go on.
三 二 一...
Three, two, one...
停 停
Stop! Stop!
没关系 洒了就舔回去
Oi, no, spillage is lickage, it's fine.
- 继续吧 艾姆  - 太恶心了
- Go on, Em!
- That is disgusting.
你在干什么
What you doing?
- 不 不 不 不...  - 啊
- No, no, no, no...
- Yeah!
我看到了 那是作弊
I saw that.
That was cheating.
你知道兽医诊所在哪里吗 因为我有两只生病的天鹅
Do you know where the vet's are? '
Cause I got two swans that are sick.
我从来没有做过爱
Never have I ever had sex.
别闹了 我们又不是12岁的孩子
Fucking hell!
Come off it, we're not 12.
我从来没有一天晚上跟两个人睡过
Never have I ever slept
with two birds in one night.
我才不喝 因为我他妈是个圣人
I'm not drinking that
'cause I'm a fucking saint.
- 哎呀  - 放松
- Oi.
- Chill out.
假期发生的事情就留在假期里吧
What happens on holiday stays on holiday!
- 你为什么要那么说  - 我只是开玩笑 宝贝
- What are you doing?
- I was only joking, babe.
很显然我又没把你拖进来
I wasn't going to call you out, obviously.
当然
Yeah, sure!
没有人在乎你是不是处女 没人在意
No one cares if you're
a virgin, it's very chill.
那你为什么要提起它呢
So, why are you bringing it up, then?
因为这很有趣
'Cause it's funny.
这不好笑
It's not funny.
斯凯 这不好笑
Skye, it's not funny.
喝一杯吗
Got a drink?
不过 帕迪很性感
Paddy is fit, though!
你应该和他试试
You should try it with him.
不然的话我就上了
Or I might.
不错啊 老板
Oi, matchy-matchy, night bossman.
这些人简直跟你妹妹一样酷
Top graft on these lot, they're
about as cool as your sister.
放松点 我们在度假呢
Chill out, mush, we're on holiday!
怎么了
What's the matter?
你听到了吗 他们在谈论我们
Did you hear?
They're talking about us.
千万不要暴露我们的年龄
We need to, like, not
let on our age at all.
- 别让他们知道  - 嗯
- To them.
- Yeah.
我好想念我的宝马车啊
Ooh, I miss my BMW so much!
真狡猾
Subtle!
听着 听着
Listen. Listen.
你觉得佩吉是同性恋吗
Do you think Paige is gay?
你在开玩笑吗
Are you joking?
- ...我不知道  - 你在开玩笑吧
- J... I don't know.
- Are you joking?
- 你在开玩笑吗  - 真希望她是同性恋
- Are you telling a joke?
- Let's hope she's gay.
她当然是
Of course she's gay.
多亏了我
I saved that!
- 直接逆转局势  - 别扯了 它是直挺挺进去的
- Tipped it straight over.
- Don't lie. That went right in.
- 妈的  - 那可是作弊
- Fuck off!
- That's cheating.
- 好吧 来吧  - 你怎么还坐下了
- Right, come on.
- Look at you sat down.
- 快点 - 不
- Come on.
- No!
搞什么
What the fuck!
来吧
Let's go.
来吧 都喝了
Come on, get it down you.
来吧
Come on Badger.
啊 啊 马利亚
Uh, ah, Malia!
帕迪 动起来
Oi! Paddy! Move.
我还没准备好呢
I'm in a bad way!
...二 三
...two, three!
感觉好些了吗
Feeling any better?
没有
No.
我想我可以帮忙
I think I can help.
前几天我卖掉了我的吸尘器
So, I sold my
hoover the other day, yeah?
嗯
Yeah.
因为它一直都在落灰
'Cause all it was doing was collecting dust.
等等 我还有别的
Think! I got more,
I got more.
李子和兔子有什么区别
What is the difference between
a plum and a rabbit?
我不知道
I don't know.
一个是紫色的 一个不是…
One is purple, and one isn't...
- 等一下 不 我说错了  - 哦
- Oh, wait! No,
I got it wrong.
- Oh!
是我弄错了
I got it wrong.
不不不...
No, no, no...
你很好
You're good.
说实话 我不觉得你一无所有
I don't think you've got
anything else left, to be honest.
为什么...为什么你从来没有看到有猪躲在树上呢
Why... Why do you never
see pigs hiding in trees?
因为它们很擅长
'Cause they're pretty good at it.
嘿 那是什么
Oi, what's that?
你这个小骗子
Nah! Nah...!
You little cheating bastard.
这都能骗到你 我去 我去
No, that's a classic one. I'm going,
I'm going.
该睡觉了
Bedtime.
起来吧 女孩儿们
Come on, girls.
Up you get, you beautiful lot.
巴士还有五分钟就到了 快走吧
Buses for Crush in five. Let's go.
快点儿 快走
Oi! Hurry up!
Crush is happening!
走啦
Let's go!
还有五分钟 门口见
See you at gate in five!
不
No.
不止五分钟吧
Surely, we have more than five minutes, no?
为什么要这么对自己啊
Why are we doing this to ourselves?
不 如果已经开始了 我们就得赶紧行动了
No, if it's started, we
got to get a move on.
我们可能会晚一点儿
We can be a bit late.
天啊
Oh, my God.
- 快点  - 看看他
- Come on.
- Look at the state of him.
一会儿见 好吗 来吧
See you in a bit, yeah?
Come Badger.
我什么都没带
I didn't bring any.
把这个穿上
Oi! Put this on.
他刚才说什么
What did he just say?
他身材真好
He's so fit.
我浑身都疼
Everything hurts.
我还以为...
I think that with this...
- 斯凯 这要怎么弄  - 穿下面
- Skye, how does this work?
- Underneath.
遮一遮你下面
You need to cover your bits.
我真的 你们能不能有点儿常识啊
I swear to God, you
guys need to get some life!
现在唯一的办法就是再喝一杯
The only way through this
for me is with another drink.
- 别了  - 那叫什么 缓解宿醉的那个
- No!
- What's that called?
Dog of hair?
- 是那么说的吗  - 是啊
- Dog of hair!
- Hair of dog.
- 都一样 - 是的 我妈妈总是这么做
- That's a thing.
- Yeah, my mum does it all the time.
看到了没 就是这样
See? It's proper.
别让我给你穿衣服 我才不是你妈
I'm not fucking dressing you.
I'm not your mum.
- 谢了 老妈  - 直发器呢
- Thanks, mum.
- Where's the hair straighteners?
不 等等 斯凯 我还得穿点儿别的
No, wait, Skye,
I need something else on with it.
- 什么 什么  - 都能看到里面了
- What? What?
- It's see-through.
哪有
It's not that see-through!
在水里不就能看见了吗 我们要去的不是泳池派对吗
In the water it will be.
I thought this is a pool party.
来啊 就是那样
Right come on orange!
Come on, that's it.
加油 女孩儿们
Come on, girls!
Let's get it down you!
加把劲儿啊 用上你们的胸器
Use those double
-Ds!
他们是怎么不会被呛到的
How are they not choking on that?
就是这样 女孩们 加油
That's it, girls! Double
-Ds, babes!
赢家已经诞生了 干得好
We have a winner!
Well done, babes.
干得好 先生 太棒了
Well done Sir, that's fantastic.
还有人要来吗
One more girl! Anyone!
- 塔兹 塔兹  - 不 斯凯
- Taz! Taz!
- No, Skye.
这里 塔兹
We've got one here! Taz!
绿衣服的吗 来吧
In the green, yeah? Come on!
来吧 你可以的 你可以的
Come on, baby girl, you
got this one, you got this!
我们有一个勇敢的男士来啦
One brave boy to play the game.
快看他 他很想参加
Hey, here we go.
Look at him, he's eager.
- 你还好吗 兄弟 准备好了吗   - 是的是的
- You all right, bruv? Ready?
- Yeah. Yeah.
去吧 兄弟
Right, up there you pop.
Go on, son.
上吧 塔兹
Go on, Taz. Whoo!
- 哦  - 你好 小花
- Oh!
- Hello, little flower.
你好吗
How are you?
- 你还好吗  - 是的
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- 接下来是谁  - 我是塔拉
- Who've we got?
- I'm Tara.
你好 塔拉
Hello, Tara!
你知道这是什么游戏吗
You know what this kind of game is?
- 大概吧  - 这可有点儿小流氓 你确定吗
- I guess so.
- It's a bit naughty.
Are you sure?
看到了吗 他有一个看起来像是啤酒的假鸡巴
All right, he's got a big
fake willy, that looks like a beer,
你要做的就是喝掉所有的啤酒
and you're going to drink it.
准备好了吗
Right, ready?
嘴里含着啤酒 像吹箫一样 来吧 来吧
Beer in the mouth, blowjob-style.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
就是这样 就是这样 继续 你得回去
That's it, that's it!
Go on, get back in there!
就是这样 弄到眼睛里可不行
That's it! Not in her eyes.
就是这样 继续 加油啊 继续
That's it. More, more, more, more.
Go on, keep going. Push it. Push it!
加油 伙计 就是这样 就是这样 就是这样
Put your back into it, mate.
That's it, that's it, that's it!
继续 继续
Keep going, keep going!
加油 就是这样
Get in there!
That's it, that's it, that's it!
来吧 还要张的更大些  天啊
Come on, open your mouth more,
Jesus Christ!
这样可不行 没有哪个男孩儿会喜欢的
No boy's going to be happy with you!
天啊
Christ!
虽然很糟 但我还是很爱你
Tragic. I love you though.
我不太擅长那个游戏
Yeah, I'm not good at that game.
我不知道 但是你看起来很棒
I dunno, you look pretty good to me.
- 拜托了 伙计们  - 还有人吗
- Come on, guys! All right!
- Another one?
- 可以了  - 可以了
- That's enough.
下来 下来  你输了
Off, off! You lost.
你输了 姑娘
You lost, girl!
回房里拥抱吧
You can cuddle in your own time.
- 再来一个男孩  - 再来一个
- Right, we need another boy!
- One more boy, please.
燥起来
Come on!
你们玩得很开心 对吧
You had a good time, yeah?
我看看都有谁举起手了 啊
Let me see those hands up! Yeah?
如果你手里拿着酒 就赶紧喝掉吧
If you've got a drink
in your hands, down it!
来吧 来吧 喝掉吧
Go! Now! Go, go, go! Down it!
漂亮 我喜欢
Beautiful, I like that.
他妈的还有谁
Who else is fucked?
你们在哪里
Where are you?
等等 没关系
Wait, it's fine.
没坏呢
It's still fine.
It still works.
不 不 住手
No, no! Stop it!
放开我
Aah, get off me.
你不觉得他很性感吗
Don't you think he's kinda fit, yeah?
要我说 他就是个十足的乡巴佬 不是吗
I mean, he's a complete clown, no?
那也是个性感的
No, but a sexy clown.
别这样 我觉得他很会开玩笑
Come on, I think he's proper jokes.
才没有
Nah, he's butters.
你可以找到更好的
You can do much better.
走吧
Come on.
塔兹
Taz!
是的 马利亚 是的
Yes, Malia! Yes!
今天晚上不错吧 啊
What you telling me, guys,
you had a good night, yeah?
我们要让你们都欲火焚身了
We're about to get
you lot so fucking horny.
他妈的快准备好
So fucking ready!
来吧
Let's have it.
来吧 伙计们
Let's fucking have it Malia!
Come one guys.
对不起 我刚才踩到你了
Sorry, I just stepped on you.
我们醉了 我们他妈醉了
We're drunk.
We're fucking drunk.
好了 我们再来最后一个游戏
OK, we're going to play a game.
We're going to play a last game.
今晚的最后一个
Final game of the night, yeah?
- 很疯狂  - 也很出格
- It's a mad one.
- It's a big one.
你们必须全力以赴 好吗 我们需要什么来着
You got to give it your all, okay?
What do we need?
- 你要去吗  - 如果你和我一起的话
- You going to do it?
- If you do it with me.
好啊
Yeah, OK.
来吧...
OK, let's do this...
快点
Come on.
再来一个人
One more, right?
最后一场了
Final! It's the fucking final, guys.
赶紧来吧 别藏着了
Get your game faces
on. Stretch it out! Ready?
我们现在需要两个男孩上台
We need two boys
up on this stage now.
来两个男孩儿
Get me two boys!
- 谁来 举手  - 这么多人吗
- Who've we got? Hands up!
- So many hands!
我听不到
I can't hear you.
谁要来
Who's wants it?
哎呀哎呀 看看这是谁
Oi, oi, look who it is.
上一轮的失败者  来吧 蓝衣服的小子
Yes, let's have our loser from
earlier back, come on, in the blue.
来吧 这次来证明一下自己吧
Let's get you up.
Prove yourself this time.
来吧
Let's go!
- 还有谁  - 让我看到你来
- Who we got here?
- Up you get, up you get, up you get!
巴杰
Badger.
Badger!
巴杰来了
Over here we got Badger!
巴杰 巴杰 巴杰
Badger! Badger! Badger!
孩子 你叫什么名字
What's your name, boy?
我叫汤姆 我来自他妈的伦敦
My name's Tom and I'm from fucking London!
来自他们的伦敦的汤姆
Tom from fucking London, yeah!
我们喜欢伦敦人
We love a Londoner!
现在 听着 我们正在玩的游戏
Oi! Now, listen up,
the game we are playing
就是这两个可爱的男孩必须他妈的硬起来 好吗
is these two lovely boys have
got to get fucking hard, all right?
- 我们需要几个女孩儿  - 有吗 快来
- We need some girls!
- We need some fucking girls.
- 来吧...  - 哦 不
- Come on...
- Oh, no.
真是个幸运儿
Oh, this one's a lucky boy, eh?
你们在这儿分散开
Three girls over here.
That's it, over here!
That's it.
这可真的是个技术活儿 我们看看这些男孩儿能不能撑住
That is amazing technique.
How are you not hard?
哦 天哪 她都快口吐了
Ooh, Jesus Christ, she's gagging.
来吧 巴杰  伙计
Come on, Badger, go
to your happy place, mate.
加油 女孩们 就是这样
Go on, girls!
That's it!
就是这样 我的天啊
That's it! Oh, my God!
哦 妈的
Yeah! My fucking boy!
继续 亲爱的 继续 深喉他
Let's go, darling.
Go on, deep-throat him.
没错 没错
Yes! Yes!
我们怎么说的 我们他妈的怎么说的
What are we saying?
What are we fucking saying?
他硬了 巴杰硬了
Yes, yes, yes! He's hard!
Badger is hard!
斯凯
Skye?
怎么了
Yeah.
我能去床上了吗
Is that bed free yet?
嗯
Yeah, mate.
来吧
Go on.
顺便把你的锅也带着
And take the pan with you, innit?
哦 操
Oh fuck!
谢了
Thanks.
你笑的这么开心 是有事情要说吗
You've got a big smirk on your face.
Have you got something to tell us?
说吧
Go on!
来啊 他快没时间了
Go on, get in there!
He just got a second.
拜托了 巴杰
Please, Badger.
我还在想你们什么时候会出来呢
I wondered when youse lot would surface.
早
Morning.
感觉不舒服吗
Not feeling too good, lass?
吃点早饭吧 第二轮很快就要开始了
Get some brekkie down
ya, round two starting soon.
见鬼 你真的是很难受 是吗
Fucking hell, you're really in
for the worst, aren't you?
我还以为你们这些南方的小仙女很会开派对呢 真没想到
I thought you southern fairies knew
how to party, you fucking jokers.
现在已经不好笑了
Don't feel very jokes right now.
好吐 宝贝
Gorgeous, pet!
操
Fuck!
怎么这么早
Why so early?
我什么都不记得了
I don't remember anything at all.
塔兹在他们那里吗
Is Taz at theirs?
肯定的
Must be.
你这是在作弊 宝贝
Eating's cheating, babe.
哦 天哪 别吃了
Oh, my God, please stop.
你又让我觉得想吐了
You're going to make me sick again.
怎么 你想要一些吗
What, you want some?
喂 帮个忙 把塔拉叫醒
Oi, do us a
favour and wake Tara up.
我俩还有点儿事儿
Me and her have got some unfinished business.
现在我们都知道你是怎么搞得了 巴杰
We all know how you
finish your business now, Badger.
准备好游泳了吗
You lot up for pool?
- 是的  - 什么
- Yeah.
- Em?
- 是啊  - 最糟糕的是 是的
- Yeah.
- Worst bit is, yeah,
我什么都不记得了
I've got no memory of it.
那可能是我这辈子遇到的最棒的事了
Probably the greatest thing to ever happen
to me in my whole entire life.
但是毫无记忆
No memory.
就那吗
That was the best thing?
希望这些女孩也有同样的感觉
Hopefully, them girls feel the same.
是的 我希望她们也都不记得了
Yeah, I hope they don't remember it either.
你的生活听起来很糟糕
Your life sounds proper shit.
漱漱口吧
Rinsed.
哎呀 昨晚真的很疯狂 你知道吗
Oi! Last night were crazy, you know?
塔兹 出来吧
Taz, come out here! Mush!
别叫了 你这个疯子
Stop screaming, you lunatic.
好吧 如果你们不把她带出来的话…
Well, if you won't get her out here...
她没和你在一起吗
She's with you, no?
她不是在你那里吗
Yeah! Ain't she at yours?
她怎么会在这里
No, why would she be here?
但是她和你一起回来了
Well, she came back with you.
她不在你身边吗
She not at yours?
他是在开玩笑呢 叫她出来就好
He's joking about.
Just bring her out.
我不是在开玩笑
On my Mum's life,
I'm not joking.
看看手机
Check your phone.
她肯定有发信息
She would've said something.
她总是这样
This is typical Tara behaviour.
总是一个人
She's always on one.
看吧 最后一次见到是在公寓里
See, last seen in the apartment, now.
该死
Damn!
我猜那女孩有艳遇了
I guess girl got laid.
那她把手机留在这里干嘛
What she doing leaving her phone here?
- 你怎么这么奇怪  - 我没有
- Why are you being weird?
- I'm not.
- 喂 去看看 好吗  - 对啊 看一下
- Oi, just look proper, yeah?
- Yeah, check.
如果她来了我会知道的
Mate, I'd know if she came here.
她肯定还在外面
She's definitely still on it.
我不喜欢这样
I don't like it.
先冷静点儿
Just chill out.
没什么大不了的 别太惊慌了
It's nothing major, is it?
Just fucking stop panicking.
你应该动作快点的 兄弟
Should have moved quicker, bro.
别嫉妒啊 她不适合你
Don't you get jealous, you.
It doesn't suit you.
你到底想说什么
What are you trying to get at?
她到底去哪儿了
Where is she, then?
- 废话连篇的  - 我不知道
- You chat shit.
- I don't know.
我不能就这么坐在这儿等着 我去和前台谈谈
I can't just sit here.
I'm going to talk to reception, okay?
泳池见
See you down the pool, yeah?
走吧
Come on, boys, let's go.
你来吗
Badger, you coming?
你想过来放松一下吗
Do you want to come and chill here?
我为塔拉感到骄傲 伙计
I'm so proud of Tara, man.
骄傲吗
Proud?
我打赌她肯定是...
I bet she's finally...
她想了很久了
She's wanted to for so long.
你在说什么
What are you on about?
她是个十足的处女
She's a massive virgin, mate.
你觉得她还好吗
Do you think she's all right?
嘿 她正在享受一生中最幸福的时光
Mate, she's having the time of her life.
你会嫉妒吗
Are you jealous?
不 这…不是 只是…
No, it's... it's not that, it's just...
那行 我们可以去找她
Well, we could go looking for her.
是啊 这是个好主意
Yeah, maybe that's a good idea.
真是个幸运儿啊
Ho, ho, this one's a lucky boy, eh?
亲爱的 我们走吧
Let's go darling!
继续 深喉他
Go on, deep throat him.
天哪 她快要口吐了
Jesus Christ, she's gagging.
嗨 亲爱的
Hi darling.
嘿 你怎么在这儿
All right, you?
- 帕迪  - 你在干什么呢
- Paddy!
- What are you doing?
嗯…夜不归宿
Um... not going home.
已经过了你睡觉的时间了吗
Is it past your bedtime already?
其他人呢
Where's everyone else?
还在继续吧
Still going, I think.
是吗 哦 不行 你不能去睡觉
Yeah? Oh, come on,
you can't go to bed.
我们要撑到最后
Me and you are always last ones standing.
你不会丢下我一个人吧
You're not going leave me
on my own, are you?
去海滩吗
We go to beach?
走吧 我知道你想去
Come on! I know you want to.
走吧
Come on!
- 坐那儿吧  - 这儿吗
- Sit there.
- Here?
你不喜欢这里吗
You don't fancy the strip, then, no?
- 不喜欢  - 为什么
- No.
- Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不觉得这很烦吗
Don't you think it's mad how, like,
到处都是沙子
sand just gets everywhere?
不 我们可是在海滩上呢
No, we're on a beach.
你在说什么
What are you on about?
是的 但是 到处都是
Yeah but, it just gets everywhere.
我以前没注意到 但你确实很漂亮 你知道吗
I've not noticed it before,
but you're proper beautiful, you know?
你是在恭维我吧
Some kind of compliment in there somewhere.
不过你喜欢我们中的谁 不是吗
You're into our lad, though, aren't you?
所以 到底是谁
So, what are you into, then?
意大利面和奶酪薯条
Pasta and cheesy chips.
还在开玩笑你
You're fucking jokes, you!
我们去裸泳吧
Oi, let's go skinny dipping.
- 不要  - 为什么
- No.
- Why?
- 因为天气太冷了 - 快点儿 走吧
- 'Cause it's so cold.
- Come on! Come on!
帕迪 不 不
Paddy, no! No!
帕迪 不 我不想去 放我下来
Paddy, no! I don't want to!
Put me down!
不
Paddy! No!
不 放我下来
No! Put me down!
- 只要进去了就没事了 - 完全没有 好吧 帕迪
- It's all right once you're in it!
- It's not, alright at all Paddy.
真他妈冷啊
It's fucking freezing!
过来
Come here.
你会把牙都冻光的
You're going to lose all your teeth.
过来
Come here.
你笑什么
What you laughing at?
帕迪 住手
Paddy, stop!
- 什么  - 住手
- What?
- Stop.
好吧 我不会碰你的
All right, I won't touch you.
啊 算了
No!
- 过来吧  - 什么
- Come here.
- What?
太冷了
I'm cold!
真不公平 抱着你我都不会暖和
I think it's a bit unfair how
it don't work both ways, though, really.
太冷了
I'm cold.
那走吧
Come on, then.
不是我 老板
Weren't me, boss!
什么
What?
它在我面前晃来晃去的 我控制不住
I can't help it when it's wiggling
in front of me like that, can I?
你这么紧张干什么
What are you so uptight for?
我没有
I'm not.
我以为你是个有趣的人
I thought you were the fun one.
- 你冷吗  - 嗯
- Are you cold?
- Yes.
来吧
Come on.
穿着湿衣服会更冷的
Wet clothes make you colder.
冷静点 我又不是在向你求婚 好吗
Chill out, it's not like I'm
asking you to marry me, is it?
这是什么意思
What do you mean, this isn't the wedding?
可以吗
Yeah?
我可以吗
嗯
Yeah.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
塔拉
Tara.
你呢
What's yours?
菲
I'm Fi.
- 各位 这是塔拉 - 塔拉
- Oi, you lot, this is Tara.
- Tara!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
是的 抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
跟你一起的人呢
Where's your mates at?
我们分开了
We got split up.
你还想续场吗
Do you want to come back?
要吗 快点
Yeah? Come on.
等等   一 二…好了
Right, oi, wait! Hold!
One, two... right!
走啊
Move!
走吧 我们那儿还有一场呢
Let's go. Party back at our place!
塔拉 塔拉 塔拉
Tara! Tara! Tara!
三 二 一
Three, two, one!
这太棒了
That was stunning!
你睡沙发吧 我和乔什一起
You can sleep on the sofa,
I can go in with Josh.
不用 不用
No, no, no.
我稍微睡下就行了
I'm just going to have a quick nap,
不用麻烦了
and then, then I'll be fine.
- 那可不行  - 没关系的
- That's not happening.
- It's fine.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
所以 你和乔什是情侣吗
So, like, are you and Josh together, like?
不 不 我们就像是一家人一样
No, no, no, no, we're,
like, we're, like, basically family.
- 好了 来吧 说真的 进来  - 不了
- No, right, come on, seriously, in!
- No!
- 来吧  - 这里就很舒服
- Yes!
- This is comfy!
好吧 至少待在屋里 大家都很好
Well, at least just stay inside.
Everyone's, like, proper sound.
不了 我知道 大家都很好 但是这样我会更舒服
No, I know, everyone is so nice,
but I'm... this is good for me.
好吧 好吧  要是你需要我们的话我们就在屋里
All right, fine.
Okay, but you know where we are if you need us.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Night!
- Good night.
看看谁回来了
Guess who's back!
嘿
Hey!
- 塔拉  - 我就说
- Tara!
- I fucking told you lot.
搭扣
Snap!
好 好 好 你赢了
Right, right, right.
That's one that you've won.
是啊 好吧...
Yeah, alright...
你必须...
You must have...
搭扣
Snap!
快点儿 说说细节
Come on, details!
你要说什么
You were going to say?
不过是一个疯狂的晚上而已
It was a sick night.
那么 你和佩奇…
So, did you and Paige...?
没呢 我们本来打算今天下午去 但是...
No, we were going to this afternoon, but...
我不知道 我想...
I don't know,
I think...
我觉得她有点紧张 你知道吗
I think she's kind of nervous, you know?
别转移话题
Don't change the subject.
你去哪儿了
Where've you been?
我真的吓坏了
You know, I was really freaking out.
而且还把手机留在这里了
And, what, you left your phone here, too.
塔兹
Taz.
我 我和帕迪睡了
I, I slept with Paddy.
不可能
No fucking way!
什么时候 怎么发生的
When? How did that happen?
在沙滩上
On the beach.
哦 在海滩上
Oh, on the beach!
听起来还挺浪漫
Sounds really romantic.
没有
No.
怎么样
Was it good?
然后我在俱乐部里遇到了一些很厉害的人
And then I met these
absolute legends in a club,
我们跳了几个小时 然后回到了他们的别墅
danced for hours, and then
went back to their villa.
虽然这真的很疯狂 但他们也真的很酷 所以…
And it was really mental,
but they were really cool, so...
我整个晚上都在那里
I was there all night.
所以 我错过了什么
So, what did I miss?
你和谁睡了
Who was it?
还藏着掖着呢
Oh, you're proper sneaky, you know?
我们得团结一致
All of this, we got to stick together,
互相支持 好吗
have each other's back, blah-blah-blah.
逃跑 做爱 再找新的人
Runs off, has sex and gets new mates.
所以到底是谁
Who was it?
是帕迪
Paddy.
天啊
Oh my God!
真是假日浪漫啊
Holiday romance brewing!
不是
No.
你不觉得他什么都没跟你们说很奇怪吗
Don't you think it's weird that
he hasn't said anything to youse?
不会啊
No.
我是说 这种事不会再发生了 不是吗
I mean, it'll defo happen again, won't it?
赶紧回去吧
Hey, come on.
Let's get back into it.
有很多值得庆祝的事情 不是吗
There's much to be celebrating, ain't there?
再来点儿 你的都喝完了吗
Get some more shots in!
You run out of shots?
- 好吧 再来 - 没错 来啊 来啊
- All right, shots!
- Yeah, shots, shots!
敬塔兹 他妈的传奇人物
To Taz, the fucking legend!
没错
Yes!
开始第四轮吧
Round four, let's go!
- 谢谢 - 呃
- Thank you.
- Ugh!
- 你没事吧  - 嗯
- You all right?
- Yeah.
那就行 一会儿见 白色派对
Right! I'll see you lot later.
White Party.
- 我们这儿也有派对呢 - 好
- We'll have pres here.
- Yeah.
昨晚真是个笑话
Last night was very jokes.
嘿 塔兹
Oi, Taz.
你觉得今晚你还会和帕迪一起睡吗
Do you think you're going
to sleep with Paddy again tonight?
嗯 不会了
Mm, no.
伙计们 我妈发信息了
Guys, Mum's just text.
他们肯定是知道结果了
The results, apparently they've got them.
天啊
Oh my God.
- 我不想看 - 我要去洗澡了
- I don't think I can look.
- I'm going to shower.
你不看吗
You not going to look?
不看 我肯定搞砸了
No, I know that I fucked it.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
她说我成功了
She said I did it.
我就知道你可以的
Oh my God, yes mate,
I knew you'd smash it!
听着 你随时都可以重考 好吗
Look, you can always retake, okay?
现在不用担心 好好玩儿玩儿
Just don't worry about it for now.
Just have a good time,
等你回家我们再说这些 好吗
and we'll talk about
it when you're home, okay?
我们爱你
We love you.
我真是个天才
Guys, I'm a fucking genius.
是的 你就是 贱人
Yes, you are, bitch!
- 塔兹 开门- 塔兹 去开门
- Taz, get the door.
- Taz, go get the door.
- 我才只弄了一根睫毛   - 警察 开门
- I've only got one eyelash on.
- Police! Open up!
啊哈 你们都被逮捕了
Ah! We got you there!
我们在泳池边见过的 希望你不介意
Yo, we met these down at t' pool.
Hope you don't mind.
越多越好 你们要喝一杯吗
No, the more the merrier.
Do youse want a drink?
- 来一轮吧  你有多少  - 好
- A shot? Well how many you got?
- Yeah.
- 等等 你叫什么名字  - 杰玛
- Wait, what's your name?
- I'm Gemma.
- 杰玛  - 利亚
- Gemma.
- Leah.
杰玛 利亚 我是斯凯 这是艾姆
Gemma, Leah,
I'm Skye, this is Em.
- 塔拉 - 给我一个杯子
- Tara.
- Em, send me a cup!
- 抓住  - 抱歉 宝贝
- Catch.
- Fucking hell.
Sorry, love.
我知道天秤座是什么样子
I know what a Libra looks like
气球呢
Where's them balloons then?
来吧 我们出去玩吧
Yeah, come on, let's
go out for a fag.
这里太热了
It's too warm in here.
拿一杯
Take one of them.
还有你
And you. Oi.
塔兹
Taz.
你还好吗
You good?
这个天才拿了十个A
Imagine, yeah, this genius got ten As!
来吧 燥起来
Let's get fucked up!
哎呀 闭嘴 你做得太他妈好了
Oi, shut up!
You did so fucking well.
- 太好了  - 等等 你看了吗
- So well!
- Wait, you looked?
是的塔兹 我说服了她
Yeah. Taz, I persuaded her, innit?
我记得你说过你不会去看成绩的
I thought you said you
weren't going to check results.
她明年也许还能和我一起去
She might even be able
to come with me next year.
别伤心 塔兹
Don't be sad, Taz.
无论你做什么 你都会很棒的
Whatever you do, you're going to be great.
我们什么时候去
When are we going?
- 这么快吗  - 来吧 塔兹
- Are we going soon?
- Come on, Taz.
会很有趣的
Oh, it's going be so fun.
白色派对
White Party!
今晚我们得盯着艾姆 她看起来已经很糟了
We got to keep an eye on Em tonight.
She's already looking fucked.
不过我们也不会照顾她
We're not going to babysit her, though.
今晚就是要查成绩的 她已经努力过了
Like, it's results night, she's worked for it.
反正你不用拿十个A就可以开一家餐馆
Pretty sure you don't need ten
As to open a restaurant anyway.
我会去前台帮你
I'll get you on front desk.
你去过哪家有前台的餐厅
What restaurant have you been
to what has a front desk?
两层的 还有各种包 那不是吗
Two coats? Any bags?
Yeah, that's four pounds!
那可不是前台 那是衣帽间
That's not front desk, that's a cloakroom!
我才不会在衣帽间工作
I'm not going to
be working on a cloakroom.
你现在可没有那么多选择
Yeah, I'm not sure you've
got much choice at this point.
好啦
Nah, come on.
我是在开玩笑的
I'm joking.
不过我就算在衣帽间里也是个笑话
I would be kinda
jokes in a cloakroom, though.
所以 帕迪活儿好吗
So what, is Paddy good, then?
是挺不错的吧
Yeah, I guess.
他知道自己该做什么 是吗
Like, he knew what he was doing, innit?
是啊 他看起来就很会
Yeah, he looks like it.
他会...
Did he, like...
把你抱起来 然后这样那样的吗
pick you up and
throw you about and that?
差不多吧
Kind of.
他很强壮
Like, he's strong.
那你应该再和他睡一次
Then you should deffo go
for round two with him.
- 那是你的  - 谢谢
- That's yours.
- Thanks.
好了 你们俩 留到卧室里再说吧
All right, you two,
save it for the bedroom.
你还好吧
You all right?
是啊 你呢
Yeah, you all right?
昨晚的事很抱歉 我当时很沮丧
Sorry about last night.
I was trashed.
你想说什么
What do you mean?
没关系的
It's fine.
操...
Fuck...
啊...
Fucking, yeah...
喝完我会头疼的
It's giving me a migraine.
试试吧 来呀
Come on then, let's have a shot.
不 我不要伏特加 我只想简单喝一杯
No, I don't want vodka,
I just want a shot. Go on.
你他妈的整个晚上都去哪儿了
Where the fuck have you been all night?
我们要去裸泳
We're going skinny dipping.
在酒店吗
At the hotel?
不是  在海滩
No, at the beach.
我很好
I'm good.
好啦 今晚是最后一晚了 别这样了
Come on! It's your last night here.
Stop being a little weirdo.
我不想弄得到处都是沙子
I don't wanna get sand everywhere.
就只是因为这破沙子吗
It's just fucking sand!
我要回去了
I'm all right.
别再像个怪胎了 塔兹
Stop being a freak, Taz.
好吧
Okay.
塔拉 过来 我只是开玩笑
Tara come on,
I'm only joking.
走吧 巴杰
Oi, come Badger.
算了 我还是送她回去吧
No. I'd better walk her back.
他妈的
Fuck!
你要干嘛去
What you doing, bro?
去海滩吗 大家都在那里
Going down t' beach?
Everyone's there.
嗯 当然咯
Yeah, of course.
来吧 帕迪都去了
Come on. Paddy's coming.
她喜欢在海滩上
She loves it on t' beach, her.
来吧
Come.
我一会儿来找你
I'll come and find you later on.
你要喝一杯吗
Do you want a drink?
喝茶吗
Cuppa?
好啊
Yeah, sure.
你更愿意成为哪一个 小山羊还是马塔宝宝
What would you rather be, a
baby goat or a mata baby?
玛塔宝贝是什么
What's a mata baby?
我不知道 宝贝 你怎么了
I don't know baby,
what's the matter with you?
你要糖吗
Do you want any sugar?
- 派对 派对 派对 - 塔兹 塔兹
- Party! Party! Party!
- Taz! Taz!
当时你在哪里 我们很想念你
Where were you?
We missed you, mate.
- 来吧 小美女 - 派对 派对 派对 派对
- Come on, gorgeous!
- Party! Party! Party! Party!
- 几点了  - 我们来这儿可不是为了睡觉
- What time is it?
- We didn't come here to sleep.
我们给你买了一份礼物
We bought you a present.
- 这里有个懒鬼  - 搞定她
- Got a dead weight!
- Sort her out.
醒醒吧 你们这些懒人
Wake up, you lazybones.
- 你根本就没 睡着 - 快点
- You're not even asleep.
- Come on!
- 你怎么了 - 派对 派对 派对
- What's the matter with you?
- Party! Party! Party!
- 喂 巴杰 烟呢  - 起床 别再偷懒了
- Oi, Badger, where's the fags?
- Get up! Stop being lazy.
嗨
Hi.
我只想说...
I just want to say...
昨晚真的太棒了
last night were amazing.
我睡着了
I'm asleep.
我只是来打个招呼
I just came to say hi.
嗨
Hi.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
睡在这里
Sleeping here.
你不喜欢吗
Did you not like it?
我给你拿了杯喝的 兄弟
Yo, I've got a
drink for you here, bro.
我可以了 哥们儿
I'm all right, me, bro.
我现在想睡会儿 我太困了
I'm good. I'm going to go to bed, me,
I'm pretty tired.
我现在已经不想跟其他人约会了
I'm a taken man now, aren't I?
你穿的是什么
What are you wearing?
我帮你脱了吧 不然会很热的
Get these off you, you'll be red hot.
帕迪 大家都在这里 我都睡着了
Everyone's here,
Paddy, and I'm asleep.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
塔兹
Taz?
塔拉
Tara?
怎么了 艾姆
Yeah, Em?
爱你
Love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too, mate.
你没事吧
You all right?
嗯
Yeah.
但...
I am
但我有点醉了
but I'm a bit pissed, though, mate.
我想明年我真的会想你的
I think I'm really going
to miss you next year.
我们还会出去玩吗
Are we still going to hang out?
当然了 我们会的
Yeah, mate, we will.
我们是一辈子的朋友
We'll be best friends for life.
别动 让我来吧
Don't move.
Let me do it.
我是不是太快了
Am I too fast?
你喜欢快的  不是吗
You like it fast, don't you?
我的脖子疼死了...
My neck is killing me...
拜托了 让我们睡睡床吧
Let us in the bed, for fuck's sake.
那地板太他妈的硬了 哥们儿 我的脖子疼死了
That floor is fucking
rough, mate, my neck's fucked.
我就说
Told you you would.
我爱你
I love you, mate.
有史以来最好的假期
Best holiday ever.
今晚可不出去了
Probably won't go out tonight.
太累了 是吗
Went a bit hard, innit?
你不能一直装听不见
You can't pretend you can't hear me.
我都已经在你的阳台上了
I made it onto your balcony now.
抱歉 我只是累了
Yeah, sorry,
I'm just tired.
醒醒
Wake up legends!
任务完成 下一个
Mission complete!
On t' next one!
再来一轮...
Round...
他妈的这是第几轮了
Fucking what round is it?
早啊 都还好吗
Morning, gorgeous.
All right?
你说什么
What you saying?
没什么 我说我很冷 兄弟
Nothing, I'm chilling, bro.
见鬼 你们好好聊吧
Fucking hell!
Good chat lads!
他是个可怕的家伙
He's a nightmare of a guy.
我从小就认识他
I've known him since I were little.
我俩儿的妈妈是好朋友
His mum and my mum, they're best mates.
我们住在一条街上
And we live on the same street.
那还挺好的
That's nice.
回家见
See you back home.
我们要南下了 嘿 是个不错的笑话
Yeah, we'll come down.
It'll be well jokes.
或者反过来说也行
Yeah, or we'll come up.
看你们北方人是怎么说的吧
See how you northern lot do it.
无论如何 我们明年都会回来
Anyway, we're all coming back next year.
同样的时间 同样的地点 肯定不会爽约
Same time, same place, no excuses.
好啊
Yeah, no excuses.
也不能早睡 塔兹
No early bedtimes either, Taz.
给她打电话 好吗
Call her, then, innit.
到家后请务必给我发短信
Make sure you text
me when you get home.
你把你的电话号码给帕迪了 是吗
You gave Paddy your number, yeah?
回头见
See you later.
- 再见  - 再见
- Bye.
- See ya.
回见 美女们
See you gorgeous!
嗯 我要去这里吃点东西
Uh, I'm going to
get some munch from here.
你要什么
What do youse want?
- 薯条 如果有卖的话  - 嗯 我也是
- Chips if they have them.
- Yeah, chips also.
快告诉我们所有的细节
Give us all the details then.
其实已经没什么了
There's not really anything to add to it.
我想我们明年还会来的
I reckon we'll come back next year.
你昨晚又做了 是吗
Oi, you did it again last night, innit?
肯定是
I swear!
第二次会更好吗
Oh, was it better the second time, yeah?
有什么好害臊的
Why are you being sheepish?
来嘛 说说啊
Come on, give us the details.
不要
No.
那不算数 根本就不算
It didn't count.
It weren't really proper.
- 怎么会呢  - 给你
- How can it not be proper?
- Here.
你们俩在说什么
What are you pair saying?
就是昨晚的事
Just saying about last night.
塔兹说那不算数
Taz is saying it didn't count.
他很性感啊
He's fit.
反正我是这么想的
In my opinion, anyway.
我也是
I would have.
是啊 他很性感
Yeah, he is fit.
谁能想到你们俩最能滚床单
Who'd have thought you two
would get laid the most?
是啊 我不知道 他就是...
Yeah, I don't know, he's just...
一个奇怪的人 不是吗
a weird guy, innit?
这是什么意思
What do you mean, he's a weird guy?
别管他了
Forget him!
我们一到家就出去 好吗
We're going out as soon
as we get home, yeah?
我们现在可以钓当地人了
We got local man to get on, now!
去他妈的帕迪
Huh! Fuck Paddy, man!
你值得更好的男人
You can do so much better.
塔兹
Taz?
我当时其实...
I like, I was...
睡着了 所以……
asleep, so...
你是说...
Are you saying...?
怎么了 塔兹 他两晚都是那样对你的吗
What, Taz, was he like
that with you both nights?
算了
It's fine.
你应该说出来的
You should've said something, like.
我都没有意识到 我...
I didn't clock, I...
塔兹...
Taz...
不 你是对的 我应该 我应该说出来的
No, you're right, I should've,
I should've said something.
没关系
It's fine.
这不对
No, it's not.
我们应该在这里买东西 这里便宜多了
We should buy stuff here.
It's much cheaper.
这个假期我甚至都没纹身什么的
I didn't even get a
tattoo or anything on this holiday.
你太忙了
You were busy.
闻闻
Oi, smell that.
很不错
It's banging, that.
...到伦敦 卢顿
- ...to London, Luton.
他妈的 你们知道这是我们的登机时间吧
Fuck! You guys know this
is our plane boarding, innit?
快走
Come on!
...大门将在五分钟后关闭...
...the gate will be closing in five minutes.
Final call...
快 快 快...
Go! Go! Go! Go...
我们不是一无所获
We got this.
我们要回家了
We're coming home!
翻译：霓虹狮子_